Guide to the Sports Memorabilia Collection SC0814
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Sports Memorabilia, Accession ARCH-2016-021
  - NFL
    - San Francisco 49ers 2010 Media Guide (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco 49ers 2014 Yearbook (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - San Francisco 49ers 50th Anniversary Collector's Edition, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Redskins 2011 Yearbook (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Official Pro Football Hall of Fame Yearbook - Class of 2011 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Official Pro Football Hall of Fame Yearbook - Class of 2011 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Pro Football Hall of Fame 2013-14 Yearbook (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Pro Football Hall of Fame 2013-14 Yearbook (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Sporting News 2014 Pro Football (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Sports Illustrated - The Year in Pictures, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Olympics
  - PGA
- Sports Memorabilia, Accession ARCH-2017-088
  - College Football Programs (mostly UCLA and USC) (Box 1)
- Sports Memorabilia, Accession ARCH-2017-159
  - Football trading cards (Box 1)
- Sports Memorabilia, Accession ARCH-2018-051
  - NFL Programs Publications
    - 49ers Game Day: 49ers vs. Chargers, 2014, Dec 20 (Box 1)
    - San Francisco 49ers Yearbook, 2015 (Box 1)
    - 49ers Game Day: Cowboys vs. 49ers, 2015 Aug 23 (Box 1)
    - 49ers Game Day: Chargers vs. 49ers (2 copies), 2015 Sep 3 (Box 1)
    - 49ers Game Day: Vikings vs. 49ers (2 copies), 2015 Sep 14 (Box 1)
    - 49ers Game Day: Packers vs. 49ers (2 copies), 2015 Oct 4 (Box 1)
    - 49ers Game Day: Ravens vs. 49ers (2 copies), 2015 Oct 18 (Box 1)
    - 49ers Game Day: Seahawks vs. 49ers (2 copies), 2015 Oct 22 (Box 1)
    - 49ers Game Day: Falcons vs. 49ers, 2015 Nov 8 (Box 1)
    - Dallas Cowboys Star (2 copies), 2015 Jan 10 (Box 1)
    - Official NFL Autograph Yearbook (3 copies), 1968 (Box 1)
    - Misc. Programs, 2015 (Box 3)
    - Sporting News Pro Football Draft, 2007 (Box 3)
    - The NFL You, 1983 (Box 3)
    - Football Fans Guide, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Football Digest, 1975 Oct (Box 3)
    - Draft Report, 1984 (Box 3)
    - Monday Night, 1979 (Box 3)
    - KC Chiefs poster (Box 3)
    - Programs, 1974-1998 (Box 3)
  - NFL Tickets
    - 49ers, 1951 (Box 1)
    - 49ers, 1971-2008 (Box 1)
    - 49ers, 2010-2014 (Box 1)
    - Colts, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Raiders, 1968-1983 (Box 1)
    - Rams, 1971-1978 (Box 1)
    - Seahawks, 1993 (Box 1)
  - NFL Ephemera
    - NFL Schedules, 2003-2012 (Box 1)
    - 49ers Magnets (Box 1)
  - Other Football Leagues
    - USFL Tickets, 1983-1985 (Box 1)
    - CFL Tickets, 1995 (Box 1)
    - WFL Press Releases, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Canadian Football League, 1964 (Box 3)
  - College Football
    - Programs - USC, Bruins, Cal, Colorado, Rutgers, Boise State, Fresno State, Sun Devils, Arizona Wildcats, UNLV, UNR, University of Arizona, Texas Longhorns, 2015 (Box 2)
    - Mile High Sports, 2015 (Box 2)
    - Cal, 1931-1952 (Box 3)
    - Gametime, 2012 (Box 3)
    - College Football News Releases, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Misc. Programs, 1921-1984 (Box 3)
    - College Football Tickets, Non-Stanford (Box 4)
  - Baseball
    - Yankees Score Card, 1947 (Box 3)
    - San Francisco Bay Area Baseball Club Score Book, 1956 (Box 3)
    - Red Sox Score Card, 1953 (Box 3)
    - Cincinnati Baseball Club Score Card, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Pacific Coast League, Oakland Baseball Club Score Card, 1942 (Box 3)
    - Fighting Phillies Score Cards, 1948-1949 (Box 3)
    - Dodgers Score Card, 1949 (Box 3)
    - Chicago Cubs Programs, 1963-1969 (Box 3)
    - Mets Program, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Penn Franklin Field Illustrated, 1931 (Box 3)
    - Cleveland Indians Score Card, 1942 (Box 3)
    - Hollywood Stars Score Book, 1941 (Box 3)
    - Modesto Nuts Playball, 2009 (Box 3)
    - National League Memo re fraternizing with spectators, 1932 Apr 9 (Box 3)
    - Oakland Athletics Programs, 1948 (Box 3)
    - Oakland Oaks Programs, 1946 (Box 3)
    - San Francisco Seals Programs, 1948-1957 (Box 3)
    - San Francisco Giants Programs, 1948-1962 (Box 3)
    - Baseball Book, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Spalding Sports Show, 1949-1952 (Box 3)
  - Olympics
    - Programs, 1956-1960 (Box 3)
  - Tennis
    - Programs, 1930-1974 (Box 3)
  - Rowing
    - Cal vs. Washington, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Boxing
    - Programs, 1933-1956 (Box 3)
    - Dempsey vs. Sharkey posters (Box 3)
  - College Basketball
    - Programs, 1970-1995 (Box 3)
  - NBA
    - Programs, 1951-1970 (Box 3)
  - Track Field
    - College Track Field Programs, 1939-1951 (Box 3)
    - Great Britain vs. USA, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Hockey
    - World Hockey Association Schedule, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
    - NHL Seals, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Sports
    - Menlo Atherton Jaycees All Sports Almanacs, 1962-1966 (Box 3)
    - Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum (Box 3)
  - Oversize Programs
    - John L. Sullivan Program (Boxing), 1880s (Box 5)
    - Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum, 1950s (Box 5)
    - Football by Clark Shaughnessy, 1910s (Box 5)
    - Olympiade, 1960 (Box 5)